<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on The Snowman Online</title>
		<link>http://thesnowman.online/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on The Snowman Online</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="http://thesnowman.online/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>Welcome to The Snowman Online</title>
			<link>http://thesnowman.online/posts/welcome/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://thesnowman.online/posts/welcome/</guid>
			<description>The Snowman Online is dedicated to helping flakes around the world with the Snowflake cloud data warehouse. The site will provide a series of blogs, tutorials and amusement for you all to enjoy and hopefully further your careers with this amazing technology.
I am just a simple Snowman. I don&amp;rsquo;t have any affiliations and my goal is just to assist and have some fun along the way. I&amp;rsquo;m always looking to improve the site so please do provide any feedback that you think may help and if you have a question please send me a mail or contact me over on twitter.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Snowman Online is dedicated to helping flakes around the world with the Snowflake cloud data warehouse.  The site will provide a series of blogs, tutorials and amusement for you all to enjoy and hopefully further your careers with this amazing technology.</p>

<p>I am just a simple Snowman.  I don&rsquo;t have any affiliations and my goal is just to assist and have some fun along the way.  I&rsquo;m always looking to improve the site so please do provide any feedback that you think may help and if you have a question please send me a mail or contact me over on twitter.</p>

<p>Happy flaking.</p>

<p>Ted (The Snowman)</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
